Getting lost is a beautiful thing.
And taking a drive
is the best way to do it.
It's where I let my thoughts wander.
Back to childhood.
Nostalgic for the past.
Or I find myself
embracing the beauty
of not knowing
what's around the next corner.
It feels like I'm searching for something,
but I don't know what that something is.
I think back to my defining moments,
the ones that helped shape me
into who I would become.
and to all those wrong turns
that led to the right decisions.
Driving deeper and deeper into the night,
down unknown roads,
to newfound places.
Further and further away
from what came before,
but closer and closer
to what comes next,
until everything around me
is unrecognisable.
That's when I know I'm lost.
But we're never truly lost.
We're searching for what moves us.